Angela Y. He

Senior Product Designer

About

I'm a product designer with 5 years of experience creating end-to-end web and mobile apps in the D2C and B2B space. I drive impact through designing new tools, and I'm a systems thinker who deeply values craft and user empathy.

Contact

www.angela-he.com linkedin.com/in/angela-he angelahe4@gmail.com

Work Experience

Arcadia

Senior Product Designer

Jul 2021 - Present

Lead designer for post-signup experience. I crafted a solar dashboard to increase customer retention and an advocacy tool that sends hundreds of emails to legislators to support solar legislation in states like California. I drive design strategy through research and visioning.

Also lead designer for solar internal tools. I created a O-to-1 inhouse tool that enabled Arcadia to scale the solar business from 30 MW to 1000 MW while reducing manual processes.

Product Designer

Jun 2019 - Jul 2021

Third product design hire. I designed new products such as a referral experience and utility connect component. Reduced customer attrition by creating a utility-specific movers flow.

Skills

User interface User experience Mobile/web design Visual design

Wireframing Prototyping Journey mapping User flows

User research Systems thinking Product strategy Design systems

HTML CSS Javascript

The Atlantic

Product Design Fellow

Jul 2018 - Jun 2019

Shaped reader experiences by revamping the entire newsletter suite and designing the Ideas section and interactive maps.

Education

Emory University
Dual-major in
Computer Science
and Visual Arts

Concur/SAP

Software Design Engineer Intern

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

Incorporated web accessibility into the travel application with front-end and WCAG standards for assistive technologies.